Good afternoon, my name is Juliet Heckman, and I'm a junior at Leon High School here in Tallahassee, Florida.
Over the past two and a half years, I've had the privilege of taking four AP courses, three of which have been history-related.
These classes have further advanced my knowledge of the world around me, as each class offers thorough evidence, viewpoints, and reasoning based on its designated topic.
When I heard the news that there was an AP course in the works that was designated specifically to African American studies, I was grateful.
Grateful in the sense that this side of history, one which is notoriously ignored and disregarded, would finally be given the proper and sufficient representation that it deserves.
I was grateful that there was an interdisciplinary course that not only goes into depth on the history of African Americans,
but also emphasizes the contributions made by them that have built the foundation of our country itself.
Now, you can only imagine how me and many of my classmates felt when we recently learned that, because we live in the state of Florida,
we would not be given the opportunity to take this course, because it, and I quote, lacks educational value.
Every single AP course that I have taken has significantly advanced my knowledge and understanding of our world,
and has inspired me to learn more, and I have full confidence that this course would be no different.
Simply because Florida lawmakers may be uncomfortable or even afraid with the course's criteria, because it is too woke,
does not grant them the right to take away this opportunity from thousands of students across the state.
Times are changing, education is expanding, and students have higher levels of curiosity than ever before.
It is not fair for our education to be constricted under the ignorant opinions of those who reject a course
that is designed to only advance our understanding of the world around us.
This is not a course of indoctrination.
It's a course that dives deep into the history, culture, arts, literature, and advancements
that African Americans have and continue to make in our country.
A greater understanding of this honest history is necessary in order to fully comprehend our country's origins
and the contributions that have been made to lead us to where we are today.
Let me tell you something about Black folks.
We're going to cheer you on when you're saying a word.
They was in the back.